UNITE Northeast Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/012 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Northeast Department Audio-Visual Materials
1985-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/012 AV
3.22 cubic feet
3.2 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
7672260
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 03, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/012: UNITE Northeast Department Files 6000/012 P: UNITE Northeast Department Photographs
Textile industry -- New York (State); Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7672260
- Fechheimer Uniforms - The Truth behind the labels, 1 (Box 1)
- Leslie Fay - Ch 22, Stop the work 3/1994, 2 (Box 1)
- Lois's tape - ch 29 - 4/13/1994, 3 (Box 1)
- Haz-Wyo Valley Dist Council 2/28/1994, 4 (Box 1)
- Ch 22 5/5/1994, 5 (Box 1)
- 3/17/1994 -- Ch 16, 6 (Box 1)
- 5/15/1994 -- Ch 22, 7 (Box 1)
- Ch 22 -- 4/24/1994, 8 (Box 1)
- Ch6 5/5/1994, 9 (Box 1)
- Haz-Wyo Dist. Council, 10 (Box 1)
- Sunday 5/14/1994, 11 (Box 1)
- WYOU TV 22, 12 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 13 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 14 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 15 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 16 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 17 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 18 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 19 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 20 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 21 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 22 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 23 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 24 (Box 1)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 25 (Box 1)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 26 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  English/Spanish version
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 27 (Box 1)
- Decision '92 Clinton YES, 1992; 28 (Box 1)
- Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, AFL-CIO, CLC, 29 (Box 1)
- Hillary Clinton Sews Union Label -- 3/6/1996, 30 (Box 1)
- The True Cost of NAFTA: a report from the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 31 (Box 1)
- Desert Storm Musical ILGWU Chorus - August 29, 1991, 32 (Box 1)
- UNITE! Stop Sweatshops Campaign -- Dec., 1996, 33 (Box 1)
- Surviving the bottom line with Hendrick Smith, 34 (Box 1)
- UNITE! - Because every vote counts, 1 (Box 2)
- ILGWU- Haz-Wyo Valley Dist. Council, 2 (Box 2)
- Mansfield, Ohio, North American Knit Workers - Support Leslie Fay Strikers (June-July, 1994), 3 (Box 2)
- Sunday 5/15/1994, Sunday 5/22/1994, 4 (Box 2)
- Senator Wofford with ILGWU strike members at Leslie Fay (June 4, 1994), 5 (Box 2)
- Ch 44 @ 8p.m., 6 (Box 2)
- Tom Harkin for President, 1992; 7 (Box 2)
- Roxanne of PA., 8 (Box 2)
- Leslie Fay Stake holders - Jim McNulty Show, 9 (Box 2)
- 3/17/1994, 10 (Box 2)
- Ch 28 -2/28/1994, 11 (Box 2)
- 4/14/1994, 12 (Box 2)
- Eye Witness Newsmakers - May 15, 1994; Leslie Fay - Sun. May 22, 1994, 13 (Box 2)
- 4/6/1994, 14 (Box 2)
- Plight of the Garment Industry (4/29/1985), 15 (Box 2)
- We do the work "Sewing our future", 16 (Box 2)
- Paula Green Advertising - ILGWU - 3/18/1994, 17 (Box 2)
- Leslie Fay Rally, NYC, 9/22/1993, 18 (Box 2)
- Leslie Fay Rally, NYC, 9/22/1993, 19 (Box 2)
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight, 20 (Box 2)
- Leslie Fay Rally, NYC,, 9/22/1993, 21 (Box 2)
- Leslie Fay: we don't buy it, 22 (Box 2)
- Future Shop: a modular manufacturing shop, 23 (Box 2)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO: Labor meets Sen. Harris Wofford, 24 (Box 2)
- An uncommon woman - Agency: Governor's Cultural Advisor (March 3, 1988), 25 (Box 2)
- An uncommon woman - Agency: Governor's Cultural Advisor (March 3, 1988), 26 (Box 2)
- ILGWU: Leslie Fay (Box 3)
  Cool 94, Erica Allen
- 8/20/1993 (Box 4)
- Fred Williams - 8/19/1993 (Box 5)
- 8/6/1993 (Box 6)
- Fred Williams - 9/1/1993 (Box 7)
- Tuesday - 8/10/1993 (Box 8)
- Radio Interview - 2/2/1994 (Box 9)
- Tuesday - 8/10/1993 (tape 2) (Box 10)
- Fred Williams - 8/13/1993 (Box 11)
- New York Boycott (Box 12)
- unlabeled (Box 13)